[
  {
    "question": "wolf",
    "answer": "狼"
  },
  {
    "question": "raise",
    "answer": "育てる、上げる"
  },
  {
    "question": "female",
    "answer": "女性の"
  },
  {
    "question": "birth",
    "answer": "誕生"
  },
  {
    "question": "dig",
    "answer": "掘る"
  },
  {
    "question": "hole",
    "answer": "穴"
  },
  {
    "question": "within",
    "answer": "の内部に"
  },
  {
    "question": "while",
    "answer": "の間ずっと"
  },
  {
    "question": "hunt",
    "answer": "狩る、捜す"
  },
  {
    "question": "instead",
    "answer": "その代わりに"
  },
  {
    "question": "behind",
    "answer": "後ろに"
  },
  {
    "question": "guard",
    "answer": "を守る、を見張る"
  },
  {
    "question": "history",
    "answer": "歴史"
  },
  {
    "question": "tie",
    "answer": "きずな、ネクタイ、を結ぶ"
  },
  {
    "question": "culture",
    "answer": "文化"
  }
]
